Daisy (Jiayi) Zhu

 $jia 1222@uw.edu \mid (206) 631-1392 \mid \underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/jiayi-zhu-0702861a4/}$

Profile: https://shorturl.at/acLMP

QUALIFICATION SUMMARY

With four years of digital marketing experience, I've consistently delivered effective strategies to boost brand visibility and engage audiences. I excel in utilizing digital channels like social media, SEO, content marketing, and paid advertising to meet marketing goals. Incorporating my multidisciplinary knowledge and effective communication skills, I facilitate cross-functional collaboration to ensure alignment and understanding among diverse teams.

RELEVANT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Meany Center for Performing Arts (Seattle, WA)

Digital Marketing Coordinator

Oct. 2022-Present

- Orchestrated the development and implementation of social media content strategy, crafting digital assets to drive brand visibility, audience engagement, and ticket sales while maintaining a cohesive visual identity.
- Spearheaded community management efforts across multiple social media platforms, fostering engagement and expanding online presence.
- Participated in the website redesign project by conducting user research and card-sorting exercises.

Pack Up + Go (remote)

Jun.2023-Aug.2023

Social Media Video Content Intern

- Produced 60+ engaging video and photo pieces for surprising travel website social media channels on platforms like TikTok and Instagram, resulting in a 30% increase in engagement.
- Used Sprout Social to analyze performance metrics and adjust strategy to grow the audience.
- Collaborated with creative team to maintain brand consistency and foster influencer collaboration.

TikTok (Shanghai, China)

Jan.2022-Sep.2022

Employer Branding Strategy

- Used Canva to create on-page ads, wrote guidelines and helped other teams optimize the process.
- Operate the official TikTok account, @lifeatTikTok, engineered and delivered 20+ targeted social media campaigns along with 80+ marketing materials such as social media postings and brochures to promote brand awareness on YouTube and TikTok.
- Created creative short videos for TikTok, wrote captions and proposed the use of A/B testing to find the best caption for short videos to increase traffic and exposure, published short videos with over 100,000+ exposures.
- Evaluated the effectiveness of paid advertisements on LinkedIn and TikTok, assessing metrics such as click-through rates, conversion rates and more.

KPMG Corporate Advisory (Shanghai, China)

Mar.2022-Sep.2022

Employer Brand Marketing Coordinator

- Lead the pre-planning and planning phase of the new employee recruitment campaign, including the development of the KPMG "Leave Your Mark" campaign strategy and negotiations with various vendors. Participate in the development of event guidelines.
- Produced posters and promotional videos to disseminate event information through various social media channels, attracting the attention and participation of over 10,000 fans.
- Successfully organized 3 mixed online and offline events with a total of 3,000 + participants.

Hill & Knowlton Public Relations Consultant (Shanghai, China)

Mar.2021-Dec.2021

Integrated Marketing Coordinator

• Conducted research on media backgrounds and information, continuously maintained an up-to-date media database, built relationships with more than 80 key media entities, facilitated event partnerships, fostered strong connections, and garnered favorable media reviews.

 Serviced Bridgestone Tire brand, assisted in the development of a comprehensive communications strategy, prepared quarterly evaluation reports, researched competitor trends, and made recommendations for improvement.

Dentsu Media - iProspect (Shanghai, China)

Mar. 2020-Jan.2021

Search Engine Optimization Assistant

- Tracked clients' voices on social media platforms and compared them with competing companies.
- Identified 5 competitors, and articulated best practices for user engagement, and community.
- Produced 480 pieces of content with high-frequency search terms on different platforms, which resulted in a 70% increase in click-through rate through improved search rankings

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Chatbot Design for UW Foster MSBA & MSCM programs

Product Manager

- Provided daily progress updates to stakeholders and facilitated coordination and communication among team members.
- Organized usability testing scripts and scheduled participant interviews, conducting and managing the interview process and report logs efficiently.
- Actively participated in chatbot content structure initiatives.

Seattle Coffee Map

Data Analyst

- Developed a Seattle coffee map using Python and the Yelp API.
- Conducted comprehensive assessments of coffee shop ratings within specific regions.
- Made insightful comparisons between independent coffee establishments and chain franchises.

XR Community Building Chess Game

UX Designer

- Improved player experiences with user-centered design and user testing.
- Developed prototypes using Unity3D and Unreal Engine, adding XR features like gesture controls and haptic feedback.

Video Storytelling for ICHS

Video producer

• Produced an educational video for ISCH (International Community Health Services) by conceptualizing strategies and ideas, collaborating with the team, and handling video shooting and editing.

EDUCATION

University of Washington (Seattle, WA)

Jun. 2024

Master of Digital Media and Communication GPA:3.97/4.0

Shih Hsin University (Taipei, Taiwan)

Jun. 2021

Bachelor of Public Relations and Advertising GPA:3.93/4.0

SKILLS

Time management, Communication, Critical thinking, Collaboration, Project management, Leadership, Video Storytelling, Data analysis, Paid ads & PPC Campaign, Google Analytics, Video editing, SEO and SEM, XR design, Graphic design Python, Chatbot design, GitHub, Figma, Miro, Canva, Adobe Suite